http://www.hydromine.co.za/privacy-policy

HomeNewsAbout HydromineProductsApplicationsLFC™ Pressure Regulating Valve StationsLFC™ Flow Control SystemPump Station AutomationLFC™_1B Range Of Medium To High Pressure Valves
LFC™_1B Electrically Actuated ValvesLFC™_1B Manual Isolation ValvesLFC™_1B Nitrogen Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_1B Pilot Operated Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_1B Spring Acting Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_1B Surge Prevention ValveLFC™_1B Pressure Regulating ValvesLFC™_1B Pressure Control ValvesLFC™_1B Water Hydraulic Actuated ValvesLFC™_3B Range Of Low Pressure Valves
LFC™_3B Electrically Actuated Valves LFC™_3B Pilot Operated Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_3B Spring Acting Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_3B Surge Prevention ValveLFC™_3B Pressure Regulating ValvesLFC™_3B Pressure Control ValvesLFC™_3B Water Hydraulic Actuated ValvesLFC™_3B Pilot Operated Pressure Regulating ValveLFC™_5E Range Of Surge Reduction Check ValveLFC™_7 Range Of Energy DissipatersLFC™_22 Pinch Type Manual Isolation Valve (BARET Valve)LFC™_22 Pinch Type Surge Prevention Valve (BARET Valve)HMP™_6A Range Of Surge Reduction Check ValveHMP™ Pipe Jointing Couplings
HMP™ -TE Range of Taper Pipe CouplingsHMP™ U-Coupling (Taper Pipe Coupling)HMP™ Range of Hydraulic Pipe CouplingsHMP™ Range of Threaded Pipe CouplingsHMP™ Range of StrainersHMP™ Expansion BellowsHMP™ Pipe Fittings, Flanges & FabricationHMP™ Steel FlangesHMP™ Spiral Wound & Ring GasketsHMP™ Heavy Duty Fire Hose ReelsHMP™ Pressure GaugesPiping FabricationOur Team & ServicesProjectsAgenciesContact
PRODUCT RANGE
ApplicationsLFC™ Pressure Regulating Valve StationsLFC™ Flow Control SystemPump Station AutomationLFC™_1B Range Of Medium To High Pressure ValvesLFC™_1B Electrically Actuated ValvesLFC™_1B Manual Isolation ValvesLFC™_1B Nitrogen Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_1B Pilot Operated Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_1B Spring Acting Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_1B Surge Prevention ValveLFC™_1B Pressure Regulating ValvesLFC™_1B Pressure Control ValvesLFC™_1B Water Hydraulic Actuated ValvesLFC™_3B Range Of Low Pressure ValvesLFC™_3B Electrically Actuated Valves LFC™_3B Pilot Operated Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_3B Spring Acting Surge Relief ValvesLFC™_3B Surge Prevention ValveLFC™_3B Pressure Regulating ValvesLFC™_3B Pressure Control ValvesLFC™_3B Water Hydraulic Actuated ValvesLFC™_3B Pilot Operated Pressure Regulating ValveLFC™_5E Range Of Surge Reduction Check ValveHMP™_6A Range Of Surge Reduction Check ValveLFC™_7 Range Of Energy DissipatersLFC™_22 Pinch Type Manual Isolation Valve (BARET Valve)LFC™_22 Pinch Type Surge Prevention Valve (BARET Valve)HMP™ Pipe Jointing CouplingsHMP™ -TE Range of Taper Pipe CouplingsHMP™ U-Coupling (Taper Pipe Coupling)HMP™ Range of Hydraulic Pipe CouplingsHMP™ Range of Threaded Pipe CouplingsHMP™ Range of StrainersHMP™ Expansion BellowsHMP™ Pipe Fittings, Flanges & FabricationHMP™ Steel FlangesHMP™ Spiral Wound & Ring GasketsHMP™ Heavy Duty Fire Hose ReelsHMP™ Pressure GaugesPiping Fabrication
Print
Email
Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of our clients. This privacy policy statement is designed to help you understand what information we gather online and what we do with that information. Because our Web site will continue to implement new technologies and improve the services and features we provide, this policy is subject to change without prior notice. For that reason, we encourage you to review the privacy policy periodically. By using our Web site, you agree to the terms of the privacy policy in effect at that time.
Our Privacy Principles:
We do not sell client information.
We do not allow those who are doing business on our behalf to use our client information for their own marketing purposes.
Information We Gather
The type of information we gather online is summarized into general categories. The following explains why we collect this information and how we use it.
1. General Tracking Information
We keep track of the pages visited by each user. Our Web server automatically collects some information about you when you request pages from our server, including your IP address. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.
We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our site by making it more responsive to the needs and preferences of our users. This information does not identify you personally.
On occasion we may provide this aggregate information to vendors, investors, potential advertisers, or news agencies to demonstrate the amount of interest in the site and to help us plan for technical infrastructure requirements.
2. Contact Information
We keep record of all contact made through our website on our database. We use this to respond to your enquiry and may use your contact information for future marketing. None of this information will be sold to outside organizations.
TEAM & SERVICES
ABOUT US
AGENCIES
HOME
PRODUCTS
CONTACT US
PROJECTS
TEAM & SERVICES
P.O. Box 751307, Gardenview, 204748 Angus CrescentLongmeadow Business Park East Johannesburg
JOIN OUR MAILING LIST
LEGAL INFO
Terms And ConditionsDisclaimerPrivacy Policy
Copyright © 2020. Hydromine™ Products (Pty) Ltd | Website By Capture Creative
.
